# **ERICK ALONSO TORRES MARAVILLAS**

**WEB SUPPORT ANALYST** 







Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico



www.linkedin.com/in/erick-alonso-torres-maravillas

# ABOUT ME

I am a proactive person, an excellent team player, organized, and responsible. I greatly enjoy learning new things, so my goal is a challenging and dynamic position where I can share my experience and, at the same time, acquire new knowledge in regards the transformative power of technology.

## EDUCATION

#### Centro Universitario de Ciencias Exactas e Ingenierías

**Engineer in Communications and Electronics** (2017-2022)

- Academic score 92.89
- Final Project as a Graduation Method: Oral irrigator with electronic power selector.

# COURSES

- The web Developer Bootcamp 2022 HTML, CSS & Javascript
- The complete Javascript course 2023: From Zero to Expert! (Udemy course)
- C++ programming, basic to advance 2022.

# SKILLS

- HTML
- Javascript
- **JQuery**
- CSS
- Salesforce
- Content Management Systems
- Node.IS
- **Bilingual Customer Service**
- Tech Support

# LANGUAGES

#### **Spanish**

Oral level - native Written level - native

## Inglés

Oral level - B2 Written level - B2

# JOB EXPERIENCE

# Web Support Analyst I

Q4. (May 2023 - Present)

· Responsible for updating investor websites for various global companies, using tools like CMS, HTML, JS, jQuery, and CSS.

# **Customer Service / Order Management**

KenislT. (January 2022 - April 2023)

· Registration of drug delivery orders for patients and hospitals across the United States of America.

#### Maintenance Staff

Towanda Summer Camp. (June 2021 - September 2021)

- Maintenance staff at a summer camp located in
- Pennsylvania, U.S.A.
- Working in carpentry, plumbing, roofing and electricity.

# Bilingual customer service agent

Comcast Company. (June 2016 - May 2021)

- · Resolution of billing questions, account management and sales.
- · Remote technical support. Responsible for solving problems regarding cable, internet and telephone equipment using ticketing and management systems.